This is Kristaps Porzingis.
Seven foot three.
One of the most skilled big men in basketball.
In 2025, he was diagnosed with POTS.
Postural orthostatic tachycardia syndrome.
When he stands up, his heart rate can hit nearly 130 beats per minute.
POTS means a jump of 30 or more, just from standing.
If it can slow down a seven-footer in the NBA...
...think about everyone else who has it.
POTS is one of the most reported problems in long COVID.
Right now, about 17 million American adults have it.
79 percent say it limits their daily activities.
Between 2 and 4 million are out of work because of it.
That's about 170 billion dollars in lost wages. Every year.
Harvard economist David Cutler put the total cost at...
3.7 trillion dollars.
For an illness most people think is over.
Porzingis has NBA doctors.
Most people with long COVID don't.
Follow for more.